<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE supplementalData SYSTEM "../../common/dtd/ldmlSupplemental.dtd">
<supplementalData>
	<version number="$Revision$"/>
	<transforms>
		<transform source="Ethi" target="Ethi_Sarb" direction="both" draft="contributed" alias="Ethiopic-Musnad" backwardAlias="Musnad-Ethiopic">
			<tRule><![CDATA[
########################################################################
# SERA 1997 System
#
# The BGN/PCGN system for Amharic Was designed for use in romanizing
# names written in Amharic characters. The Roman letters and letter
# combinations shown as equivalenS to the Amharic characters reflect
# modern Amharic pronunciation. Different consonant characters in three
# groups are pronounced alike in modern Amharic and are therefore
# romanized identically for use in geographic names.
#
# Prepared by Daniel Yacob <yacob@geez.org>
#
# Based on the 1994 Romanization Systems and Roman-script Spelling
# Conventions document. The 2005 draft has been consulted, but contains
# errors, which if relevant are pointed out in this file.
#
########################################################################
#
# MINIMAL FILTER: Ethiopic-Musnad
#
:: [:Ethiopic:] ;
#
########################################################################

########################################################################
#
# Define All Transformation Variables
#
########################################################################
#
#
$alternate  = \`;
#
#
# Use this $wordBoundary until bug 2034 is fixed in ICU:
# http://bugs.icu-project.org/cgi-bin/icu-bugs/transliterate?id=2034;expression=boundary;user=guest
#
$wordBoundary =  [^[:L:][:M:][:N:]] ;
#
########################################################################
#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER HE
#
[áˆ€-áˆ†] â†’ ð© ;
áˆ€ â† ð© ;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE LA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER LAMEDH
#
[áˆˆ-áˆ] â†’ ð©¡; 
áˆˆ â† ð©¡; 

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE HHA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER HETH
#
[áˆ-áˆ—] â†’ ð©¢; 
áˆ â† ð©¢;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER MEM
#
[áˆ˜-áˆŸ] â†’ ð©£;
áˆ˜ â† ð©£;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER SHIN
#
[áˆ -áˆ§] â†’ ð©¦;
áˆ  â† ð©¦;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER BETH
#
[áˆ¨-áˆ¯] â†’ ð©£;
áˆ¨ â† ð©£;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER SAT
#
[áˆ°-áˆ·] â†’ ð©ª;
áˆ° â† ð©ª;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER QOPH
#
[á‰€-á‰] â†’ ð©¤;
á‰€ â† ð©¤;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER RESH
#
[á‰ -á‰§] â†’ ð©¨;
á‰  â† ð©¨;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER TAW
#
[á‰°-á‰·] â†’ ð©©;
á‰° â† ð©©;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER KHETH
#
[áŠ€-áŠ] â†’ ð©­;
áŠ â† ð©­;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER NUN
#
[áŠ-áŠ—] â†’ ð©¬;
áŠ â† ð©¬;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER ALEF
#
[áŠ -áŠ§] â†’ ð©±;
áŠ  â† ð©±;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER KAPH
#
[áŠ¨-áŠµ] â†’ ð©«;
áŠ¨ â† ð©«;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER WAW
#
[á‹ˆ-á‹Ž] â†’ ð©¥;
á‹ˆ â† ð©¥;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER AYN
#
[á‹-á‹–] â†’ ð©²;
á‹ â† ð©²;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER MEM
#
[á‹˜-á‹Ÿ] â†’ ð©¸;
á‹˜ â† ð©¸ ;
á‹˜ â† ð©¹ ;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER YODH
#
[á‹¨-á‹®] â†’ ð©º;
á‹¨ â† ð©º;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER DALETH
#
[á‹°-á‹·] â†’ ð©µ;
á‹° â† ð©µ;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER GIMEL
#
[áŒˆ-áŒ•] â†’ ð©´;
áŒˆ â† ð©´;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER TETH
#
[áŒ -áŒ§] â†’ ð©·;
áŒ  â† ð©·;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER SADHE
#
[áŒ¸-áŒ¿] â†’ ð©®;
áŒ¸ â† ð©®;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER DHADHE
#
[á€-á†] â†’ ð©³;
á€ â† ð©³;

#
# ETHIOPIC SYLLABLE MA - OLD SOUTH ARABIAN LETTER FE
#
[áˆ-á] â†’ ð©°;
áˆ â† ð©°;

#
#
# Inverse Fiter : Latin-Ethiopic
#
:: ([:Old_South_Arabian:]) ;
#
########################################################################
			]]></tRule>
		</transform>
	</transforms>
</supplementalData>
